=== Category of Posts ===
Contributors:  Linda MacPhee-Cobb
Requires at least: 2.0
Stable tag: 1.0


== Description ==
This will create a list of all your posts in one specific category.  They will be ordered alphabetically by category.  
You can put this as a list in your side bar, a page or a post


== Installation ==

1) Download, unzip, upload to your plugin directory and active the plugin.

2) Go into your Admin page find Options->Posts by category

3) Put the number of the category you want to list in the box and click 'Update options'

4) Add the following code to your sidebar:

<?php echo category_of_posts() ?>

OR

4) Add the following code to a post or page <!-- listacategory -->


== Frequently Asked Questions ==

If you need more information try here:
http://herselfswebtools.com/2007/10/here-is-a-quick-way-to-print-a-list-of-all-your-posts-by-category-in-wordpress.html

